{"name": "65D  2008-4", "questions": [{"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "1. If m = 4, n = -5, and p = 9, what is the value of mp - mn?", "choices": {"A": "16", "B": "31", "C": "41", "D": "56", "E": "81"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "2. Vehicle A averages 19 miles per gallon of gasoline, and Vehicle B averages 37 miles per gallon of gasoline. At these rates, how many more gallons of gasoline does Vehicle A need than Vehicle B to make a 1,406 mile trip? ", "choices": {"A": "28", "B": "36", "C": "38", "D": "56", "E": "74"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "3. If  and , then ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "8"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "4. If 12(x - 7) = -11, then x = ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "5.  The legs of a right triangle measure 18 m and 24 m, respectively. What is the length, in meters, of its hypotenuse?", "choices": {"A": "21", "B": "30", "C": "42", "D": " ", "E": ""}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "6. In the school cafeteria, students choose their lunch from 4 sandwiches, 2 soups, 2 salads, and 2 drinks. How many different lunches are possible for a student who chooses exactly 1 sandwich, 1 soup, 1 salad, and 1 drink?", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "4", "C": "10", "D": "16", "E": "32"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "7. What is  of 63% of $6,000 ?", "choices": {"A": "$34,020", "B": "$4,200", "C": "$3,402", "D": "$420", "E": "$42"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "8. DMC Electronics Company builds 2 products: a DVD player and a VCR. Employees of the company can build a maximum of 150 DVD players per week and a maximum of 200 VCRs per week. No more than 250 products can be built per week. In the following inequalities, d represents the number of DVD. players and v represents the number of VCRs. Which inequality expresses the constraint on the number of products built per week?", "choices": {"A": "d + v \u2264 150", "B": "d + v \u2265 200", "C": "d + v \u2264 200", "D": "d + v \u2265 250", "E": "d + v \u2264 250"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "9. In the figure below, \u2220ADC measures 50\u00b0, \u2220ACB measures 65\u00b0, and \u2220BAC measures 90\u00b0. What is the measure of \u2220BAD ?", "choices": {"A": "105\u00b0", "B": "115\u00b0", "C": "130\u00b0", "D": "140\u00b0", "E": "155\u00b0"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "10. Which of the following is equivalent to (2x + 3)(x - 7) ?", "choices": {"A": "2x2 - 21 ", "B": "2x2 - 11x - 21 ", "C": "2x2 + 11x - 21 ", "D": "2x2 + 17x - 21 ", "E": "2x2 + 17x + 21 "}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "11. A baker has  cups of sugar in her pantry. Each cake she bakes requires  cup sugar. Which of the following is the largest number of whole cakes for which she has enough sugar in her pantry?", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "3", "C": "8", "D": "9", "E": "10"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "12. If f(x) = 6x2 + 4x - 11, then f(-5) = ?", "choices": {"A": "-181", "B": "-119", "C": "61", "D": "119", "E": "159"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "13. Which of the following expressions is equivalent to - x2 - x ?", "choices": {"A": "-x(x + 1)", "B": "-x(x - 1)", "C": "-x(1 - x)", "D": "x(x + 1)", "E": "x(x - 1)"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "14. The student body at Julian High School consists of sophomores, juniors, and seniors only. The ratio of sophomores to juniors  to seniors on Julian High School's student council is 2:3:4. There are 15 juniors on the student council. How many students are on the entire student council?", "choices": {"A": "21", "B": "24", "C": "45", "D": "60", "E": "135"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "15. The second term of an arithmetic sequence is -14, and the third term is -34. What is the first term?(Note: In an arithmetic sequence, consecutive terms differ by the same amount.)", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "6", "C": "14", "D": "20", "E": "-20"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "16. Last year, Tom earned an annual salary of $S from which a total of $D was deducted for taxes and insurance. The balance was Tom's take-home pay. Tom's take-home pay represents what fraction of his annual salary?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "17. Mara is the timer for a road race. She is 200 feet from the starting gun. Using 1,120 feet per second for the speed of sound, which of the following is closest to how many seconds after the starting gun is fired that Mara will hear the starting gun?", "choices": {"A": "0.1", "B": "0.2", "C": "0.6", "D": "0.9", "E": "1.3"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "18. What is the slope of the line represented by the equation 6y - 18x = 6 ?", "choices": {"A": "1", "B": "3", "C": "6", "D": "18", "E": "-18"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "19. At a buffet restaurant, the price for dinner for an adult is $6.95 and the price for dinner for a child is $3.95. A group of 8 people weht to the restaurant for dinner and paid a total of $46.60, excluding tax and tip. How many adults were in the group?", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "3", "C": "4", "D": "5", "E": "6"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "20. The graph below shows the distance, d miles, you are from home t hours following the start of a walk. Which of the following statements accurately describes your walk?", "choices": {"A": "You start at home, and after 2 hours are 12 miles from home.", "B": "You start at home, and after 2 hours are 6 miles from home.", "C": " You start 12 miles from home, and after 2 hours are home.", "D": "You start 12 miles from home and after 2 hours are 6 miles from home.", "E": "You start 6 miles from home and after 2 hours are 12 miles from home."}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "21. In right triangle \u25b3XYZ below, cos Z = Which of the following expressions is equal to cos X ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "22. For any nonzero value of y, (y-5)3 = ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "y8", "D": "y15", "E": "y125"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "23. The ratio of the side lengths of 2 similar triangles is 3:5. The smaller triangle has sides that measure 5 centimeters, 7 centimeters, and 9 centimeters. What is the perimeter, in centimeters, of the larger triangle?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "21", "C": "35", "D": "63", "E": "105"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "24. Points R(6,4) and S(-4,5) lie in the standard (x,y) coordinate plane. What is the slope of RS ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "25. In the figure below, E is a point on side AB of rectangle ABCD. The measures given are in inches. What is the area of \u25b3DEC, in square inches?", "choices": {"A": "10", "B": "12", "C": "16", "D": "20", "E": "32"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "26. Use the following information to answer questions 26-28.Fran is planning to fence a 10-foot-by-15-foot rectangular plot of ground to use as a garden. She intends to plant a 1-foot-wide border of flowers along the inside of the entire perimeter. The rectangular section surrounded by this border will be planted with vegetables in 11-foot-long rows parallel to the longer sides.What is the minimum number of feet of fence Fran would need to enclose the garden if there will be a 3-foot-wide opening on one side of the plot for people to walk through?", "choices": {"A": "22", "B": "25", "C": "47", "D": "50", "E": "150"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "27. Use the following information to answer questions 26-28.Fran is planning to fence a 10-foot-by-15-foot rectangular plot of ground to use as a garden. She intends to plant a 1-foot-wide border of flowers along the inside of the entire perimeter. The rectangular section surrounded by this border will be planted with vegetables in 11-foot-long rows parallel to the longer sides.What is the area, in square feet, of the rectangular plot?", "choices": {"A": "50", "B": "104", "C": "126", "D": "146", "E": "150"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "28. Use the following information to answer questions 26-28.Fran is planning to fence a 10-foot-by-15-foot rectangular plot of ground to use as a garden. She intends to plant a 1-foot-wide border of flowers along the inside of the entire perimeter. The rectangular section surrounded by this border will be planted with vegetables in 11-foot-long rows parallel to the longer sides.When Fran plants the vegetables, she wants the center lines of adjacent rows to be at least 10 inches apart. She also wants the center lines of the outermost rows to be at least 10 inches from the inner edge of the flower border. According to these planting restrictions, what is the maximum number of 11-foot-long rows of vegetables that could be planted within this garden plot?", "choices": {"A": "8", "B": "9", "C": "10", "D": "11", "E": "12"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "29. If | x + 9 | = 19, what are the possible value of x?", "choices": {"A": "-28 and 10", "B": "-10 and 10", "C": "-10 and 28", "D": "-9 and 9", "E": "10 and 28"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "30. In the standard (x, y) coordinate plane, M(9, -8) is the midpoint of TW. If W has coordinates (3, 1), what are the coordinates of T?", "choices": {"A": "(15, -7)", "B": "(15, -17)", "C": "(6, )", "D": "(6, -9)", "E": "(6, -15)"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "31. If the circumference of a circle is 96\u03c0 centimeters, what is the radius of the circle, in centimeters? ", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "24", "C": "48", "D": "96", "E": "192"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "32. A  rectangular tabletop is 14 inches wide and 48 inches long. Which of the following is closest to the length, in inches, of the diagonal of this tabletop?", "choices": {"A": "34", "B": "50", "C": "55", "D": "62", "E": "68"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "33. Rectangle ABCD has vertices in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane at A(-4, -2), B(-4, 3), C(2, 3), and D(2, -2). A translation of rectangle ABCD is a second rectangle, A'B'C'D', with vertices A'(4, -12), B'(x, y), C'( 10, -7), and D'( 10, -12). What are the coordinates of B'?", "choices": {"A": "(3, -6)", "B": "(4, 3)", "C": "(4, -7)", "D": "(4, -13)", "E": "(6, -5)"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "34. The solution set for x of the equation x2 + nx - 8 = 0 is {-2, 4}. What does n equal?", "choices": {"A": "-8", "B": "-6", "C": "-2", "D": "2", "E": "6"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p>Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.</p><p>The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA)<span> </span>is<span> </span>an index of stock<span> </span>values. The chart below gives the DJIA closing values from August 24 through September 30 of a certain <span>year and the change in the closing value from the previous </span><span>day. A minus sign indicates a</span><span> </span><i>decline (a</i><span> closing value less than the previous day's closing value). A plus sign indicates an</span><span> </span><i>advance </i><span>(a closing value greater than the previous day's closing value).</span></p><p>Dow Jones Industrial Average Closing Values</p><p><img height=\"287.68\" src=\"https://ame-1253155612.cos.ap-beijing.myqcloud.com/96e820ec04bc4f1f2f8ed6640a5b47ab\" width=\"400.58\"/><br/></p>", "question": "35. Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA) is an index of stock values. The chart below gives the DJIA closing values from August 24 through September 30 of a certain year and the change in the closing value from the previous day. A minus sign indicates a decline (a closing value less than the previous day's closing value). A plus sign indicates an advance (a closing value greater than the previous day's closing value).Dow Jones Industrial Average Closing ValuesWhich of the following is closest to the percent of decrease from the August 24 closing value to the September 30 closing value?", "choices": {"A": "7.9%", "B": "8.9%", "C": "11.3%", "D": "12.7%", "E": "88.7%"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p>Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.</p><p>The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA)<span> </span>is<span> </span>an index of stock<span> </span>values. The chart below gives the DJIA closing values from August 24 through September 30 of a certain <span>year and the change in the closing value from the previous </span><span>day. A minus sign indicates a</span><span> </span><i>decline (a</i><span> closing value less than the previous day's closing value). A plus sign indicates an</span><span> </span><i>advance </i><span>(a closing value greater than the previous day's closing value).</span></p><p>Dow Jones Industrial Average Closing Values</p><p><img height=\"287.68\" src=\"https://ame-1253155612.cos.ap-beijing.myqcloud.com/96e820ec04bc4f1f2f8ed6640a5b47ab\" width=\"400.58\"/><br/></p>", "question": "36. Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA) is an index of stock values. The chart below gives the DJIA closing values from August 24 through September 30 of a certain year and the change in the closing value from the previous day. A minus sign indicates a decline (a closing value less than the previous day's closing value). A plus sign indicates an advance (a closing value greater than the previous day's closing value).Dow Jones Industrial Average Closing ValuesThe chart shows 4 more declines than advances. All of the following statements are true. Which one best explains why the decline from the August 24 closing value to the September 30 closing value was relatively large?", "choices": {"A": " The greatest change in the chart was a decline.", "B": "The least change in the chart was an advance.", "C": "The greatest number of consecutive declines was greater than the greatest number of consecutive advances.", "D": "The first change was a decline.", "E": "The average of the declines was much greater than the average of the advances."}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p>Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.</p><p>The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA)<span> </span>is<span> </span>an index of stock<span> </span>values. The chart below gives the DJIA closing values from August 24 through September 30 of a certain <span>year and the change in the closing value from the previous </span><span>day. A minus sign indicates a</span><span> </span><i>decline (a</i><span> closing value less than the previous day's closing value). A plus sign indicates an</span><span> </span><i>advance </i><span>(a closing value greater than the previous day's closing value).</span></p><p>Dow Jones Industrial Average Closing Values</p><p><img height=\"287.68\" src=\"https://ame-1253155612.cos.ap-beijing.myqcloud.com/96e820ec04bc4f1f2f8ed6640a5b47ab\" width=\"400.58\"/><br/></p>", "question": "37. Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA) is an index of stock values. The chart below gives the DJIA closing values from August 24 through September 30 of a certain year and the change in the closing value from the previous day. A minus sign indicates a decline (a closing value less than the previous day's closing value). A plus sign indicates an advance (a closing value greater than the previous day's closing value).Dow Jones Industrial Average Closing ValuesWhat is the average closing value for the 5-day period from September 13 through September 17?", "choices": {"A": "7,895", "B": "7,920", "C": "7,964", "D": "7,980", "E": "8,090"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "38. The angle of elevation from a point on the ground to the top of a building is 37\u00b0, as shown below. The point is 75 feet away from the building. Which of the following is closest to the height, in feet, of the building?(Note: sin 37\u00b0 \u2248 0.602, cos 37\u00b0 \u2248 0.799, and tan 37\u00b0 \u2248 0.754)", "choices": {"A": "45", "B": "57", "C": "60", "D": "94", "E": "125"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "39. For trapezoid ABCD shown below, AB = 8 m, DC = 5 m, and the perimeter is 39 m. What is the area, in square meters, of ABCD ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "52", "C": "65", "D": "130", "E": "260"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "40. The average distance from Earth to the Sun, which is 9.3 x 107 miles, is about how many times the average distance from Earth to the Moon, which is 2.4 x 105 miles? ", "choices": {"A": "4 x 102", "B": "7 x 102", "C": "4 x 1012", "D": "1 x 1013", "E": "2 x 1013"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "41. Which of the following operations will produce the largest result when substituted for the blank in the expression 35_____\uff08\uff09\uff1f", "choices": {"A": "Averaged with", "B": "Minus", "C": "Plus", "D": "Divided by", "E": "Multiplied by"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "42. A circle in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane has center (7, -6) and radius 10 coordinate units. Which of the following is an equation of the circle?", "choices": {"A": "(x + 7)2 - (y - 6)2 = 100", "B": "(x + 7)2 - (y - 6)2 = 10", "C": "(x + 7)2  + (y - 6)2 = 10", "D": "(x - 7)2 - (y + 6)2 = 100", "E": "(x - 7)2  + (y + 6)2 = 10"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "43. In \u25b3XYZ, XY  XZ and the measure of \u2220X is 22\u00b0. What is the measure of \u2220X ?", "choices": {"A": "136\u00b0", "B": "79\u00b0", "C": "68\u00b0", "D": "44\u00b0", "E": "22\u00b0"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "44. What is the volume, in cubic centimeters, of a cube if the area of 1 square face is 144 square centimeters?", "choices": {"A": "36", "B": "1,728", "C": "20,736", "D": "46,656", "E": "373,248"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "45. If a number is chosen at random from the set {1, 2, 3, 4, \u2022\u2022\u2022, 12}, what is the probability that the chosen number is a factor of 12 ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "1"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "46. Jamal invested $1,000 on January 1. At the end of 9 months, during which time Jamal made no with\u001fdrawals and no other deposits, the investment has earned $75 in interest. Jamal's $1,000 investment returned an annual percentage yield closest to which of the following percents? .(Note: Interest can be estimated using I = Prt, where I is the amount of interest earned; P is the amount of money initially invested; r is the annual percentage yield that the money returned; and t is the time, in years, the money is invested.)", "choices": {"A": "12%", "B": "11%", "C": "10%", "D": "8%", "E": "7%"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "47. Consider the function f(x) = 2x2 + x. What is the value of f(f(3))?", "choices": {"A": "75", "B": "168", "C": "465", "D": "885", "E": "903"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "48. What are the possible values of y such that xy2 = 54, x &lt; 10, y &lt; 10, and x and y are integers?", "choices": {"A": "-3, 3", "B": "1, 3", "C": "1, 9", "D": "3", "E": "6"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "49. Each side of a quadrilateral is 12 cm long. Which 2 of the following must also describe this quadrilateral? I. Square (sides of equal length and 90\u00b0 angles)II. Rhombus (sides of equal length) III. Rectangle (90\u00b0 angles)IV. Parallelogram (opposite sides parallel)", "choices": {"A": "I and II only", "B": "I and III only", "C": "II and III only", "D": "II and IV only", "E": "III and IV only"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "50. The points (-2,3) and (0,1) lie on a straight line. What is the slope-intercept equation of the line?", "choices": {"A": "y = 2x - 1", "B": "y = x + 5", "C": "y = x + 1", "D": "y = -x + 1", "E": "y = -2x + 3"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "51. Each number on a list containing 100 numbers is divided by 10 to produce a second list containing 100 numbers. Each of the 100 numbers on the Second list is decreased by 2 to. produce a third list of 100 numbers. The median of the third list is x. Which of the following expressions gives the median of the original list?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "x + 2", "D": "10x + 2", "E": "10(x + 2)"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "52. Whenever (x + 4)(x - 3) &lt; 0, which of the following expressions always has a negative value?", "choices": {"A": "x - 5", "B": "x - 2", "C": "x + 5", "D": "2x ", "E": "x2 - 1"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "53. Which of the following graphs in the standard (x,y) coordinate plane represents the solution set of the inequality | x + y I &gt; 1 ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "54. The expression 4 sin x cos x is equivalent to which of the following?(Note: sin(x + y) = sin x cos y + cos x sin y)", "choices": {"A": " 2 sin 2x", "B": " 2 cos 2x", "C": " 2 sin 4x", "D": " 8 sin 2x", "E": " 8 cos 2x"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "55. The angle at which light strikes a mirror is equal in measure to the angle at which it is reflected. In the hall of the mirrors below, what is the measure of the indicated angle? ", "choices": {"A": "50\u00b0", "B": "55\u00b0", "C": "70\u00b0", "D": "80\u00b0", "E": "90\u00b0"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "56. Which of the following is the graph pf the solution set for |x - c| \u2265 2 ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": " ", "C": " ", "D": " ", "E": " "}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "57. Square ABCD is shown below in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane. The line y = ax + 2 divides the square into 2 congruent regions if a = ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "1"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "58. If log3 2 = p and log3 5 = q, which of the following expressions is equal to 10 ?", "choices": {"A": "3p+q", "B": "3p + 3q", "C": "9p+q", "D": "pq", "E": "p + q"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "59. The domain of the function  y(x) = 3 cos(5x - 4) + 1  is all real numbers. Which of the following is the range of the function y(x) ?", "choices": {"A": "-3 \u2264 y(x) \u2264 3", "B": "-4 \u2264 y(x) \u2264 3", "C": "-3 \u2264 y(x) \u2264 2", "D": "-2 \u2264 y(x) \u2264 4", "E": "All real numbers"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "60. In the figure below, both solids consist of 4 cubes, each 1 unit on a side. In the solid on the right, the 4 cubes form a rectangular prism that is 2 units long, 1 unit wide, and 2 units high. The solid on the left is the result of moving Cube D from its position above Cube C to beside it so that Cubes B, C, and D form a rectangular prism 3 units long, 1 unit wide, and 1 unit high. To the nearest percent, the total surface area of the solid on the right is what percent less than the total surface area of the solid on the left?", "choices": {"A": "0%", "B": "2%", "C": "6%", "D": "11%", "E": "13%"}, "correct": "D"}]}